Oh my god.
Hi Instagram, it's Billie Eilish and this is what is in my camera.
Okay, starting off very sweet.
This is a photo of me and my brother Phineas when he came to visit
me on tour.
I love this picture.
I love my brother so much.
There's nobody better in the world.
There we are.
Here is a photo of...
This is on tour in my green room after the show.
We were supposed to be getting ready for bed.
This was like a two-hour jam that turned into this like DIY homemade mosh pit,
which was awesome.
I'll show you.
That's my friend Alex playing guitar.
Acoustic version of Let the Body Sit on the Floor.
Next, here is a very cute photo of all of our little feet in a
photo booth.
I think this was like the last or second to last show of the whole
tour.
And our little feet are poking out of the photo booth and it's me and
my girls.
So you can see my little Jordans and then the girls little Mary Janes poking
out.
This is very dear to me.
Okay, next.
It's a plant that you see.
It looks like a hot dog long stick and it's in the wild.
Cattails, if you're unfamiliar.
They look very appealing and appetizing to me and I've always wanted to eat them.
Sorry.
We were on tour in my green room.
One of my flower bouquets had these cattails in them and I bit into one
and then it went all over everywhere.
So here's a photo of me having just bitten into a cattail and solo my
bassist wondering why I did such a thing.
OK, next, I basically have a notebook that I make everyone on tour draw a
full picture in and then sign it.
And Ava was trying to draw land with all these animals on it, and she
couldn't think of how to draw a horse and she wanted to practice.
So here's her practice of drawing a horse.
And I thought that was really unique.
Oh my god.
There's so many more photos like this.
Then, this is a video of me in Australia.
We went to a glass blowing workshop, which is like the most fun thing I've
ever done.
and here's me making what is now my favorite glass that I own that I
drink my coffee out of every single day.
And here's me making it.
It's cute.
Here's just a picture.
We have puppy rooms at every venue that we can.
Every new city that we go to, we have like a rescue org come to
the show and bring adoptable dogs.
It gives everyone a lot of good feelings and serotonin, but also a lot of
dogs get adopted this way And we just get to play with puppies all day
and it's pretty awesome.
So here's me playing with some puppies on tour.
Oh my God, get out of my face.
Okay, next.
This is actually very of note, considering Hit Me Hard and Soft, the tour, live
in 3D.
I sprained my ankle the night before shooting that.
And here is a photo of Christina, one of my best friends and my trainer.
Was icing my ankle while I was eating my dinner right after I sprained it.
That was insane that that happened.
Okay, last one, here we go.
This is from Barcelona and we went on this beautiful boat ride and then we
saw these like random kids jumping off this cliff.
It was so appealing and I climbed the mountain and here it is.
Here?
I would do that every single day if I could.
Thanks guys, I hope you enjoyed looking through my camera roll And be sure to
check out Hit Me Hard and Soft, the tour live in 3D in theaters.